忘了它，失敗者
Forget it, loser.
哦，倫巴多先生
Oh, Mr. Lombardo.
-嗨. -嗨，朋友
-Hey. -Hey, bro.
倫巴多先生，怎樣?
Mr. Lombardo, what's up?
-嘿，朋友. -嘿
-Hey, man. -Hey.
詹尼弗
Jennifer--
你看他的眼睛?
Did you see his eyes?
你在看什麼，哦?
What are you looking at, dork?
滾開
Fuck off.
我感激這些傢伙來這裏
l appreciate you guys coming down.
我在這個垃圾堆裏唯一想要的是-
The only thing l'm gonna miss in this dump is....
安靜
Settle down.
好吧，我們的高年級研修班課程已經上到一半
Well, we've come to the halfway point of our senior seminars.
安靜. 安靜
Settle down. Settle down.
- 比自修課還亂，是不是? - 不是!
-Beats study hall, doesn't it? -No!
-是你吉米? -至少在自修室還可以思考
-That you, Jimmy? -At least in study hall l can meditate.
他的意思是可以在這裏手淫.'
What he means is, ''masturbate.''
我相信你在這方面一定很有經驗，天那
Something with which l'm sure you've had hands-on experience, Kirk.
我沒有先生. 我沒有
lt wasn't me, man. lt wasn't me.
我是純潔的. 我是純潔的
l'm innocent. l'm innocent.
我們都聽到過「約會強姦」「性騷擾」這種講法
We've all heard the terms ''date rape,'' ''sexual harassment.''
就在這裏我們也討論過類似問題
We've discussed some of these issues right here in this very room.
我們今天的客人來自藍灣警察局
Our guests today come from the Blue Bay Police Department.
警探 杜奎特 和 皮裏…
Detectives Duquette and Perez...
…給我們帶來一點關於這個專題的大家需要的新看法
...are here to give us what we hope...
...will be a fresh perspective on the subject...
還有…準備回答你們任何人的任何問題
...and to address any questions that any of you might have.
大家熱烈歡迎
Now, let's give them a warm welcome.
-多謝. -我要走了
-Thank you. -l'm out of here.
-為何不先問個問題呢?. -問你媽個頭
-Why don't we begin with a question. -This prick can kiss my ass.
我剛剛說到…
As l was saying...
…我們為何不從一個問題開始
...why don't we begin with a question.
-什麼是性犯罪? -沒插進去!
-What is a sex crime? -Not getting any.
怎麼了? 那個中途退場的女孩是誰?
What's with that? She's the one who walked out.
-蘇西·托樂. -我去年抓過她
-Suzie Toller. -l busted her last year for possession.
可憐的孩子坐了6個月的監
Poor kid did six months in Camp Nine.
-六個月?第一次? -我不太理解這個判決
-Six months? First offense? -l didn't hand down the sentence.
他手腳不乾淨 我抓過她
She was dirty. l busted her.
嘿，卡羅爾
Hey, Carol.
我很感激你們，小夥子們. 謝謝
l appreciate you guys taking the time to come.
十分樂意
Our pleasure.
為什麼感覺您像個教導顧問?
Why do l get the feeling you don't like the guidance counselor?
別告訴我你看不到他以往的表現. 他是只獵犬
Don't tell me you can't see through his routine. He's a total hound.
你說寵物狗?
You mean pussy hound?
實際上，我想他是逗人發笑的那種
Actually, l thought he was kind of cute.
我會做了他
l'd do him.
抓住
Steady.
吉米 抓住船頭
Steady the bow, Jimmy.
很好
That's good.
降下主帆
Drop the main.
好吧 各位 收好索具. 大家週一見
All right, guys, let's de-rig and l'll see you all Monday.
嘿，小姐們，我需要洗車
Hey, ladies, my car needs a wash.
窗戶呢?
Do you do windows?
大夥兒幹的好. 週一見
Good work, guys. A.C., see you Monday.
-再見，倫巴多先生. -好的，巴迪
-See you, Mr. Lombardo. -All right, buddy.
好
All right.
真大，可以在上頭開派對
l could definitely party on one of those.
它是小摩托，吉米
lt's a stinkpot, Jimmy.
想做船老大 得搞那個玩意
You wanna be a real boatman, you wanna get yourself one of those.
是
Yeah.
那是一艘真正的船
That's a real boat.
謝謝你讓我進這個班
Thank you for getting me into this class.
我家老頭絕對不肯付這個錢的
No way my old man was gonna spring for the fees.
你幹活掙的 而且你也在擺弄船
Hey, you're working for it, and you're learning your way around a boat.
我也是在船上幹活掙夠大學學費的
l put myself through college working on boats.
- 勝過膩味的漢堡 - 哈哈是啊
-Beats flipping burgers. -Yeah.
我也可以玩玩?還是只有男孩可以?
Can l play too, or is it just for boys?
那週末誰幫你洗車? 倫巴多先生?
So who's washing your Jeep this weekend, Mr. Lombardo?
高年級洗車會，記不記得?
The senior car wash, remember?
洗我那輛老吉普是浪費時間
Washing that old Jeep of mine is a waste of time.
不會的，讓尼科爾和我一起幹怎麼樣
Not at all. How about if Nicole and l do it?
我們合作的很不錯
We're working as a team.
那就這樣.我星期六到沼林去
l tell you what. l'm going out to the glades Saturday.
為何不週日來?把所有泥巴洗乾淨
Why don't you come over Sunday and wash all the mud off.
成交
Deal.
我指望著媽媽來帶我，但是她沒來
l was counting on my mom to give me a ride, but she's not here.
奇怪 奇怪
Surprise, surprise.
所以我在想你能不能帶我一段路
So l was wondering if you could give me one.
倫巴多先生，你總不會讓我走路吧
Mr. Lombardo, you really wouldn't want me to walk, would you?
我意思是，我不會這麼倒楣的吧
l mean, like, something bad might happen.
-你呢 ?需要帶一程麼? -是的，但我得加上自行車
-What about you, you need a lift? -Yeah, but l got my bike.
沒問題
Hey, no problem.
好，來試試
Okay, try it.
蘇西，你需要麼? 還有一個空位
Suzie, you need a lift? We got room for one more.
天啊. 她哪裏弄的鞋子，像個雞
Jesus. Where'd she get those shoes, ''Whores 4 Less''?
再試試
Try it again.
很高興見到你走啦孩子們
Nice to see you kids getting along.
-別忘了禮拜日的事情. -不會的
-Don't forget Sunday. -l won't.
-是薩姆 倫巴多麼? -嗨，媽媽
-ls that Sam Lombardo? -Hi, Mom.
薩姆，嗨
Sam, hi.
嗨，桑德拉
Hi, Sandra.
進來喝一杯怎樣?
Why don't you come on in and have a drink.
不好意思，桑德拉，我得走了
Sorry, Sandra, l gotta run.
-嗨，倫巴多先生. -嗨，倫巴多先生
-Hi, Mr. Lombardo. -Hi, Mr. Lombardo.
嗨，小姐們
Hi, girls.
看吧，我就知道他忘了
Look. He forgot.
我沒忘記看車吧
-l knew it. -No, l didn't.
都準備好啦搞得真髒
Check out my Jeep. Nice and dirty for you.
不如等另一輛開走再幹
But you might wanna wait till the other car leaves.
那賓士不是你的?
You mean the Mercedes isn't yours too?
你知道我的那部是藍的，尼科爾
My Benz is blue. You know that, Nicole.
薩姆，我走啦
Sam, l'm leaving.
你的水管呢?倫巴多先生?
So where's your hose, Mr. Lombardo?
凱利，水管在車子前頭
The hose, Kelly, is right in front of the Jeep.
凱利 幫你洗吉普車?
Kelly Van Ryan's gonna wash your Jeep?
芭芭拉.只是找個理由
Come on, Barbara. lt's for a good cause.
薩姆真是個慈善家
Sam the philanthropist.
有人說:多幹點小事累不著人
Yeah, well, you know what they say: A little hard work never hurt anyone.
好
Okay.
-玩的開心點. -好的
-Have fun at the club. -Okay.
哇
Wow.
看起來和嶄新的一樣
Looks brand-new.
你忘了什麼嗎?
Aren't you forgetting something?
你的洗車票要給我們
Your coupon. We gotta have it.
哦，是的.那東西
Oh, yeah, that thing.
-我們為何不?… -規矩就是規矩，倫巴多先生
-Can't we just--? -Rules are rules, Mr. Lombardo.
好的，我找找
Okay, let me look for it.
倫巴多先生，有點晚了
Mr. Lombardo, we're running kind of late.
尼科爾要去曼森家?
How about if Nicole goes on to the Mansons'?
找到他給我騎
You can give me a ride when you find it.
給我幾分鐘好不好?
No, no, just give me a minute. Okay?
-走吧. -你肯定?
-Go. -Are you sure?
哦，弗蘭克. 哦，上帝
Oh, Frankie. Oh, God.
哦，上帝. 哦，上帝
Oh, God! Oh, God!
操!
Goddamn it!
-你好，這是藍灣高中. -你好
-Hello, this is Blue Bay High School. -Hello.
你的孩子 今天缺席，星期一--
Your son or daughter was absent today, Monday--
天啊!
Jesus H. Christ!
- 什麼? 恩? - 哦，沒事
-What? -Oh, nothing.
來吧
Come on.
-阿蒂，你抓了條好大的魚啊. -是條梭魚
-Art, this is a hell of a fish you caught. -lt's a barracuda.
你有空的時候
lf you weren't so busy chasing booty...
和我一起來打魚，你可以親手抓一條
...you'd have come with me and caught one for yourself.
別說你要吃這東西
Don't tell me you're gonna eat this thing.
為啥?
Why not?
這是梭魚，有毒，毒死你
lt's a barracuda. lt's poisonous. lt'll kill you.
操，我可以對跟你約會的女人說這個
Shit, man, l could say that about most of the girls you date.
桑德拉·范·賴安 電話找 薩姆
Sandra Van Ryan for Sam.
-桑德拉，什麼事? -凱利 今天蹺課了，薩姆.
-Sandra, what's up? -Kelly skipped school today, Sam.
你聽到什麼了?
Have you heard anything?
沒有
Not a word.
別擔心
Never mind.
我找到她了
l found her.
好
Pull!
聽著，薩姆，上次真不錯
Listen, Sam, it was really good seeing you the other day.
桑德拉，我現在很忙 不如--
Sandra, l'm real busy right now, so--
對我這隻船來說沒人開得比你好
l haven't found anyone who can handle my boat the way you can.
-是的，好吧-- -我知道你正在操 芭芭拉巴克斯特
-Yeah, well-- -l know you're fucking Barbara Baxter.
-那又怎樣? -好吧 也許我只能跟一個女人在一起
-So what? -So maybe l'm a one-woman man now.
可憐的 薩姆.
Aw, poor Sam.
你真想找一個藍灣女人嫁給你?
Really think you'll get one of these Blue Bay women to marry you?
-講完啦？桑德拉? -抓住關鍵，親愛的.
-Are you finished, Sandra? -Grab a clue, honey.
你是收費的 床上工夫不錯 向來不錯
You're a hired hand, a good lay. That's as far as it goes.
好好享受吧，趁現在還行
Enjoy it, while it lasts.
再見，桑德拉
Goodbye, Sandra.
放!
Pull!
你似乎把槍當心理醫生啦
You seem to find guns therapeutic.
也許我該試一下
Maybe l ought to try it.
好吧，讓我來猜猜
So let me guess.
整個週末某個男孩子都沒來惹你
Some boy didn't call and screwed up your whole weekend.
白白過一天?對不對?
So you're taking the day off. Right?
那又是你的哪個水手?
Which one of your deck hands is that?
管他哪個，只要是我想要的
Whichever one l want.
好吧，凱利，發生什麼事了?
Okay, Kelly, what's the matter?
怎麼了?
What is it?
我想爸爸
l miss Dad.
上帝
Jesus.
我也想他，有時候吧
l miss him too, sometimes.
你才不會
No, you don't.
他不應該自殺，凱利
He didn't have to kill himself, Kelly.
哦，凱利…
Oh, Kelly....
我不知道他為什麼要這麼做
l don't know why he did it.
我真的不知道
l really don't.
我能幫你什麼嗎?
Can l--?
Can l get you anything?
鎮靜片?
Do you want a Valium?
我被強姦了
l was raped.
什麼，親愛的? 我沒聽清楚
-What, honey? l can't hear you. -l said, l was raped.
什麼?
What?
我是說，我被強姦了
l was raped...
…被 薩姆 倫巴多強姦了
...by Sam Lombardo.
薩姆 倫巴多?
Sam Lombardo?
我的女兒… 在藍灣有人敢強姦!
My daughter does not get raped in Blue Bay!
你是說薩姆 倫巴多 強姦了她?
And you're saying that Sam Lombardo raped her?
那個混蛋敢對我女兒做這種事， 一定是在發昏
That son of a bitch must be insane to think he can do this to me.
我們知道您心情，范·賴安夫人…
We understand your feelings, Miss Van Ryan...
…不過 我們還是要先跟 凱利談下
...but please, we need some time with Kelly.
我們最好記錄她的單方陳述
We'd like to take her statement alone.
- 你準備好啦? - 好吧
-Are you all right with this, baby? -Yeah.
好
Okay.
要不要再等一下?
Would you like to take a break for a minute?
我只想快點兒結束
l just wanna get it over with.
我們得錄下這些陳訴
We'd like to videotape this statement.
我知道這個不好受，凱利 但這是很嚴重的指控…
l know this isn't pleasant, Kelly, but these are serious charges...
所以我們要知道你兩個之間發生的每一件事
...and we need to know everything that happened between the two of you.
準備好了嗎?
Are you ready?
他先是抓住我的肩膀
He started rubbing my shoulders.
我讓他--
I let him.
我是說，他的確討人喜歡…
I mean, he's a nice guy.
然後呢…
The next thing...
他的手在我短褲裏--.
...his hand was in my shorts.
這個，從後面.
You know, from behind.
他的手指….
His fingers....
-他的手指… -說清楚…
-His fingers.... -Take your time.
他把手指放進去--.
They were in me.
兩個地方，你知道?
Both places, you know?
他進入你的身體了嗎?
Did he put himself inside you?
是的.
Yes.
我說「不要.」 我尖叫.
I said ''Stop. '' I screamed.
我頭腦一片空白只有這個聲音在叫
I mean, that's how it sounded in my head.
他傷害我.
He hurt me.
你反抗過?
Did you try to fight him?
他把我的手腕扭在背後.
Well, he had my wrists pinned behind me.
然後怎樣?
Then what?
他一直在說，來吧來吧.
He kept saying, ''Let it happen.
來吧.
Let it happen. ''
然後他突然停下來.
And then he just stopped.
你是說，他離開啦?
You mean he withdrew?
我不知道，很難講清楚
I don't know. It's really hard to remember, exactly.
儘量想想，凱利.
Try, Kelly.
我只記得他在說 .
I know one thing he said.
他說，「不要怕. 我沒有射.」
He said, ''Don't worry. I didn't come. ''
我忘不了那些話.
I can't forget that.
他說:小女孩不能給我高潮.
He said, ''No little girl can ever make me come. ''
小女孩不能給我高潮.  上帝
''No little girl can ever make me come.'' Jesus.
還真壞.我們得搞一點物證
Too bad. We might have had some physical evidence.
怎麼了?
What?
也許根本沒有物證，因為也許什麼都沒發生
Maybe there's no physical evidence because nothing happened.
知道我的想法?我覺得她在演戲
You want my gut? There it is. l think she's acting.
我覺得是她找機會跟他單獨在一起，希望他能搞點事情
l think she set it up to be alone with him so he'd come on to her.
她很失望 因為他不肯做
She's upset because he didn't.
也許她是那樣計畫的. 也許不是
Maybe she set it up that way. Maybe not.
那傢伙應該讓讓她站那兒別動
The guy never should've had her there in the first place.
我掌握的情況是，他幹過藍灣半數的女人
The line l have on him, he's done half the women in Blue Bay.
但這個不能把他變成強姦犯
That doesn't make him a rapist.
對她使用測謊儀怎樣?
What about asking her to take a polygraph?
讓主教大人做個尿檢怎樣？
What about asking the pope to take a piss test?
這裏是藍灣.，格洛裏亞
This is Blue Bay, Gloria.
讓范·賴安家的人測謊，湯姆巴克斯特 還不得砍你
Ask a Van Ryan to take a lie detector test and Tom Baxter will cut you down.
你害怕湯姆巴克斯特? 你害怕桑德拉·范·賴安?
You afraid of Tom Baxter now? You afraid of Sandra Van Ryan?
討論結束，你們倆知道該怎麼做
End of discussion. You both know what to do.
調查他的鄰居，同事， 再跟凱利的朋友談談
Start with his neighbors, coworkers. Talk to Kelly's friends.
-你知道那對他意味著什麼. -是的
-You know what that'll mean for him. -Yeah.
你也聽到凱利的指控了. 這傢伙是混蛋.給我把案卷搞出來
And you heard Kelly's statement. The guy's dirty. Bring me a case.
好
All right.
幹得好，紀姆波 星期一見
Good work, Jimbo. l'll see you Monday.
好
All right.
他是我航海課的標兵
That's what's left of my sailing class.
跟我說吧，阿蒂
Talk to me, Artie.
凱利 范·賴安指控你強姦她
Kelly Van Ryan is accusing you of rape.
吉米告訴我的
Jimmy told me.
很顯然，我是最後一個知道的
Apparently, l'm the last one to know about it.
薩姆，我…
Sam, l....
桑德拉·范·賴安一整天都在做大喇叭…
Sandra Van Ryan has been on the horn all day...
跟學校當局的每一個人訴說
...with every member of the school board.
她在努力讓你停職
She's pushing for suspension.
難道校方只聽她的一面之辭，卻不聽聽我的?
And the board's just gonna roll over for her without hearing my side?
真是昏頭啦. 我是清白的，該死的
This is insane. l'm innocent, goddamn it.
你要相信我
You gotta believe that.
我能告訴你的就是那事就這樣掛著
All l can tell you, Sam, is hang in there.
他們相信你，一切都會恢復照舊的--
They clear you, you get reinstated--
你不明白這種事
You never get clear of something like this.
它會跟著你
lt stays with you.
一直都會跟著你
lt follows you around forever.
你需要有人幫助
You're gonna need some help, Sam.
你需要一位元律師
You're gonna need an attorney.
或者你能夠告訴我在南佛羅里達還有個律師…
Right. And maybe you can tell me which attorney in South Florida...
想在法庭上和范·賴安家族作對
...is gonna wanna go up against the Van Ryans in court.
我找肯·寶登
l'm here to see Ken Bowden.
-你有預約? -是的
-Do you have an appointment? -Oh, yeah. Sam Lombardo.
好，然後
Okay, then.
好的
Mr. Bowden, your 1 0:30's here.
請帶他進來
Will you show him in, please?
是什麼事讓你跑到城的這頭來的?
What brings you to this part of town?
好吧，我呢，直到昨天…
Well, l was, until yesterday...
我還是藍灣高中的法律輔導員
...a guidance counselor at Blue Bay High School.
那兒的一個學生指控我強姦
A student there is accusing me of rape.
男孩還是女孩?
Male or female?
-那個學生是 凱利·范·賴安 -桑德拉·范·賴安家的?
-The student is Kelly Van Ryan. -As in Sandra Van Ryan?
他媽的.我真夠運氣
As in, l'm fucked.
說說看?
Why don't you tell me about it?
-從哪兒開始呢? -就從…
-Shit, where do l begin? -Start with...
…你和這個女孩兒的關係說起吧，叫凱利的
...your relationship with the girl, Kelly.
她是我的一個學生.我是她的法律輔導員.除了這個，沒有其他關係
She's a student. l was her counselor. Beyond that, there's no relationship.
那就別擔心
You got nothing to worry about.
-你把你脖子怎麼了? -這個?
-What did you do to your neck? -This?
我不用整天帶著這個的
l don't have to wear it all the time.
先前有個保險公司的小子在那兒
There was an insurance guy around here earlier.
好吧，讓我先說說費用
All right, let me tell you how l charge.
喬治，你好.跟我說說有啥新聞？
Georgie, hey. We gonna catch some wind?
恐怕今天我不能為你停車了
Mr. Lombardo, l'm afraid l can't park your car today.
你不能為我停車? 我要和芭芭拉一起午餐
You can't park me? l'm meeting Barbara for lunch.
幫我停下車，喬治.我有點兒晚啦
Can you get this parked, Georgie? We're running late.
馬上，巴克斯特先生
Right away, Mr. Baxter.
你別上這兒來啦，倫巴多先生. 離這兒遠點兒
You're finished here, Lombardo. Take a hike.
芭芭拉，我們走
Barbara, let's go.
也許你沒聽清我說什麼，倫巴多
Maybe you didn't hear me, Lombardo.
你在藍灣完蛋啦
You're finished in Blue Bay.
如果我再發現你纏著我女兒， 你就徹底完蛋了
l find you around my daughter again, you'll be finished, period.
-滾開吧. - 倫巴多先生，請吧
-Get the fuck out of here. -Mr. Lombardo, please.
那好吧，喬治
That's all right, George.
薩姆，親愛的. 有一陣子沒見你了
Sam, honey. Haven't seen you in a while.
-歡迎回來 -朗姆酒加可樂
-Welcome back. -Rum and Coke.
你還好嗎?
Hey! Are you all right?
-我沒事. -酷?
-l'm fine. -Cool?
你這個混蛋，他媽的
That's too bad, motherfucker.
薩姆?
Sam?
倫巴多?
Lombardo?
站住，別動!是我啊
Whoa, man! lt's me.
對不起.這事兒越來越古怪了
Sorry, man. Things have been getting a little weird around here.
我明白
l can see that.
進來吧
Come on in.
你確定是 弗蘭克·亢多幹的?
You're sure this Frankie Condo guy is the guy that did this to you?
就是他，沒錯
lt was him, all right.
他開著桑德拉的車子
He was driving Sandra's Range Rover.
你把這些告訴員警，我們現在就能逮捕 桑德拉·范·賴安
You tell that to the cops, we can go after Sandra Van Ryan right now.
-這事兒算啦. -這女人很有辦法
-Forget it. -The lady has deep pockets.
我知道她多有辦法
Believe me, l know how deep her pockets are.
我想過或者我還能保住房子 有些房屋抵押貸款--
l thought l might be able to save my house. Some sort of equity loan.
猜猜誰是銀行的部門主管?
Guess who's on the board of directors at the bank?
這個女人夠給我添亂的啦
l don't need any more trouble from this woman.
你覺得是不是應該弄個訴訟來讓她住手?
You think making some sort of statement's gonna stop her?
你說凱利跟我那件鳥事? 怎麼樣
With the shit l got on Kelly? Yeah.
一年前…
A year ago...
她父親把自己腦袋打開花
...when her old man blew his brains out...
…凱利 失魂落魄，離家出走
...Kelly lost it, ran away.
他們在一家破汽車旅館裏找到她時，可卡因正搞得她魂飛天外
They found her in a fleabag motel some place, coked out of her gourd.
這當中--
Meanwhile...
…你，薩姆，在那一年當了輔導員…
...you, Sam, are voted Educator of the Year...
…也許這都是廢話
...or some crap.
他們把你們兩個推到陪審員前面…
They put the two of you in front of a jury...
…看上去很蠢. 他們知道的
...they're gonna look stupid. They know it.
為什麼他們到現在還沒來要你的呈述?
Why do you think they haven't taken your statement yet?
因為他們忙於尋找證據…
Because they're busy looking for dirt.
但他們什麼也不會發現
And they're not gonna find it.
對不對?
Right?
肯，我沒有操我的學生
Ken, l don't fuck my students.
他只是在給你表演一下
He's just showing off for you now.
嘿，那兒，魯比
Hey there, Ruby.
看來你還是跟沃爾特將就著
l see you still got Walter.
我是希望有什麼東西把他吃掉
l was hoping something had eaten him by now.
-有什麼事嗎? -蘇西給我們電話了
-Can l help you with something? -Suzie called us.
她在哪兒?
Where would we find her?
你認得路的
You know the way.
你不會開槍打她吧，啊?
You won't shoot her, will you?
我不相信她會有武裝
l don't believe she's armed.
誰呀?
Yeah?
你們路上走這麼久
Jesus, it took you guys long enough.
有人來掐死我的話時間剛好夠… 或者操我的屁股
What if someone was trying to strangle me or fuck me in the ass?
你們負責性犯罪?
l mean, you guys do sex crimes, right?
我的搭檔，皮裏警探
My partner, Detective Perez.
這是西林. 他很棒…他對賤人很有研究
lt's C?line. He's okay. He had a good line on what cheap fucks people are.
蘇西，你打電話叫我們來.記得嗎?
Yeah, so Suzie, you called us. Remember?
他們把倫巴多先生關起來啦?
Did they arrest Mr. Lombardo?
沒有
No.
- 會關他? - 我不知道
-Will they? -l don't know.
你操心這個?
That bothers you?
我想出去走走
l wanna go outside.
薩姆 倫巴多讓你搭他的便車是什麼時候?
When was this that Sam Lombardo gave you the ride?
大概一年前
About a year ago.
你是什麼時候到達的，那兒有其他人嗎?
And when you arrived at your trailer, was anyone there?
-沒有. -這麼說只有你一個人
-Nope. -So you were alone.
是
Yeah.
他和你一起進屋了嗎?
Did he come in with you?
-我想是. -你想是的.好吧，進還是沒有?
-l guess. -You guess. Well, did he or didn't he?
好吧.是，他進屋了
Okay. Yeah, he did.
然後呢?他摸你了嗎?
And then what? Did he touch you?
你，也許，有沒有跟他調情?
Did you maybe flirt with him a little?
蘇西，我知道你很難受
Suzie, look, l know you feel bad.
-但你必須告訴我們實情. -我什麼也沒跟他說
-Just tell us the truth. -l didn't say a thing to him.
他抱住我說我很好看
He just put his arm around me and told me l was pretty.
他說他想知道我是否真的好看
l could be really pretty, he said.
你有沒有要他停下來?
Did you ask him to stop?
見鬼
Shit.
這有什麼差別?不管怎樣都沒人會相信我的
What difference does it make? No one believes me anyway.
-薩姆 倫巴多強姦你了? - 是的. 好不好?他做了
-Did Sam Lombardo rape you? -Yeah. Okay? He did.
他把我推倒在地板上，然後他幹了
He pushed me to the floor and he did it to me.
- 那我們算是結束啦？ - 差不多是蘇西
-Now are we done? -Almost, Suzie.
差不多
Almost.
這麼說吧，你有沒有反抗過?
At some point, were you able to fight him off?
沒有.他自己停下來了
No. He stopped by himself.
好了吧?就是這些了?讓我一個人呆會兒
Okay? ls that it? Leave me alone.
- 別碰我! - 放鬆點…放鬆點…
-Don't touch me! -All right, take it easy. Take it easy.
他停下來了
He stopped.
就這些?他就這麼離開了?
And that was it? He just left?
是的
Yeah.
他先說過一句話
He did say one thing first.
說什麼?
What was that?
他說:「沒有小婊子能給我高潮的.」
He said, ''No little bitch can ever make me come.''
打開門
Open the gate.
- 嘿，輔導員，給支煙怎麼樣? - 你好，倒楣蛋
-Hey, counselor, how about a smoke? -Hello, Jinxy.
現在的消息是好壞各半
You know, it's really a bad news, good news situation.
你不准保釋，但你有個真正的律師…
You were denied bail, but you got a real attorney...
而不是由法庭隨便指派個辯護人
...instead of a public defender.
我告訴你，肯，我是清白的
l'm telling you, Ken, l'm innocent.
你還是對法庭的人說吧.你不是孤立無援的
You are preaching to the choir. You're not alone.
你就是那個小色鬼
So you're the new chicken licker.
桑德拉，說說你的想法?
Sandra, can we get your comment?
能談談你此時的心情嗎?
Can l just have your feelings at this time?
倫巴多 先生會得到應有的懲罰的
Mr. Lombardo will get what he deserves.
能說幾句話嗎?
Can you tell us anything?
- 您有信心打贏這場官司嗎? - 很有信心
-Are you confident about the case? -Very. Yes.
倫巴多強姦案在藍灣高級住宅區引起轟動…
The Lombardo rape case has galvanized the upscale town...
在那些小報的煽動下
...of Blue Bay with its tabloid appeal.
剛剛到達的是，桑德拉·范·賴安…
Now just arriving, Sandra Van Ryan...
大宗地產的女繼承人 藍灣上流社會的精英
...jet-set real estate heiress and part of the powerful Blue Bay elite.
從相反方向過來的是那女孩
And the girl from the wrong side of the tracks. ln the end, the jury...
到最後，陪審團要在這個18歲的女孩…
...must choose between the words of these 1 8-year-old girls...
和薩姆 倫巴多的呈詞之間作出裁決
...and that of Sam Lombardo.
這是在法院門前的現場報導… 我是新聞目擊欄目的南西·多爾
Reporting from the courthouse steps, l'm Nancy Duerr.
我是新聞目擊欄目的南西·多爾
Eyewitness News.
佛羅里達州州對薩姆 倫巴多的起訴.
The State of Florida v. Sam Lombardo.
尊敬的西維亞·B·瓦克斯曼法官 全體起立
The Honorable Sylvia B. Waxman presiding. All rise.
我們要站起來
We gotta stand up.
請坐下
Please be seated.
現在坐下
Now sit down.
還要等等，凱利?
Would you like more time, Kelly?
我知道這很難，凱利…
l know that this is hard, Kelly...
但我還要多問一個問題
...but l have one more question.
雖然大部分事實已經陳述過
And even though it's something we've been over...
但我希望我們大家完全弄清楚這件事
...l want us all to be very clear about it.
凱利，當你看到倫巴多先生…
Kelly , when you saw that Mr. Lombardo...
試圖和你發生性行為時
...intended to have sex with you...
準確地說 你如何說的?
...what were your exact words?
他說了什麼?
What did you say?
我對他說「不要.」
l told him ''No.''
我說，停下來，倫巴多先生.求你了…
l said, ''Stop, Mr. Lombardo. Please.''
我尖叫著要他停下來
l screamed for him to stop.
你尖叫著要他…
You screamed for him...
…停下來
...to stop.
那他呢?
And did he?
不
No.
他在那髒屋子的地板上強姦了我
He raped me on the floor of his shitty house.
謝謝你
Thank you.
這是倫巴多強姦案的第二天…
lt's day two of the Lombardo rape case and the second alleged young victim...
又有第二個前法律輔導員的年輕受害者…
站出來聲稱
...of the former guidance counselor has taken the stand.
昨天，凱利 范·賴安對事件做了激動的陳述
Yesterday, Kelly Van Ryan delivered an emotional account of events...
…在辯護律師的交叉質詢下毫不動搖.
...and was not swayed by defense counsel's cross-examination.
早間晚些時候我們將回到有新的進展的事件現場
We'll come back live later with an update of these proceedings.
法庭門前的現場報導… 我是新聞目擊欄目的…
Reporting from the courthouse steps, I'm Nancy Duerr...
南西·多爾
...Eyewitness News.
各位早上好
Good morning, everybody.
托樂小姐
Ms. Toller.
當你…
When you were...
還是藍灣的新生，因在商店行竊被抓時
...picked up for shoplifting your freshman year at Blue Bay...
你被允許打一個電話…
...and you were allowed to make one call...
你打給倫巴多先生. 是不是這樣?
...you called Mr. Lombardo. lsn't that correct?
托樂小姐?
Ms. Toller?
-是. -當你被開除…
-Yes. -And when you were expelled...
…因為毀壞藍灣高中的財產
...for destruction of school property--
我只是搞壞一個破窗戶.那甚至不是我的錯
l broke a fucking window. And it wasn't even my fault.
托樂小姐，你要等要求你回答時才能講話…
Ms. Toller, you will wait until you are asked before responding...
否則你會因為褻瀆法庭而受到拘訓
...and you will refrain from using profanity in this court.
倫巴多先生出席你的家長會
lt was Mr. Lombardo who appeared with you in lieu of a parent conference.
對嗎?
ls that right?
是
Yes.
在我看來…
lt seems to me...
…倫巴多先生是你的朋友
...that Mr. Lombardo was your friend.
他過去是的
He was.
但這一切都改變了，當…
But all that changed when...
…根據你的陳述
...according to your testimony...
倫巴多先生…
...Mr. Lombardo...
…強姦你…
...raped you...
…時間是去年的4月23日，對嗎?
...on April 23 of last year, is that right?
- 是. - 但是接著在5月…
-Yes. -But then in May...
…當你因為非法持有毒品被逮捕時…
...when you were arrested for possession of narcotics...
…而再次被允許打一個電話時…
...and again allowed a phone call...
…你又是打給倫巴多先生
...you called Mr. Lombardo.
-那又怎樣? -那又怎樣?
-So what? -So what?
怎樣?
So what?
你看，蘇西
Oops, Suzie.
那就是說 在你說的那個男人強姦你的僅僅一個月後，你去向他求助?
So one month after you say this man raped you, you go to him for help?
聽起來你仍然覺得倫巴多先生是一個很好的朋友
Sounds as if you still considered Mr. Lombardo a good friend.
- 我需要幫助. - 我知道你需要
-l needed help. -l'm sure you did.
但是倫巴多先生這次不在那裏
But Mr. Lombardo wasn't there this time.
那是夏天，他外出了…
lt was summer, he was gone...
你在州立管教所裏度過6個月
...and you spent six months in a state correctional facility.
那是不是讓你生氣啦蘇西，蘇西…
Did that make you mad, Suzie...
…因為薩姆外出?? 他沒在那兒?
...that Sam was gone? That he wasn't there?
就是因為這原因你才這麼說 倫巴多先生的?
ls that why you're saying these things about Mr. Lombardo...
-…說你的朋友? -我這麼說是因為它發生過
-...your friend? -l said them because they happened.
你能坐在這裏，宣誓
Ms. Toller, are you gonna sit there today, under oath...
說撒母耳·倫巴多強姦你?
...and swear that Samuel Lombardo raped you?
我說過他做了
l said he did.
我來問你一個問題.托樂小姐
Let me ask you a question, Ms. Toller.
你很喜歡做政府的客人對不對?
Did you enjoy being a guest of the state?
因為我敢肯定如果你對山姆倫巴多這事說謊的話…
Because l promise you, if you are lying about this...
而且我相信你說了謊…
...and l believe you are...
你會很快再次光臨管教所
...that you will be visiting that facility again quite soon.
那就是為什麼我要再次問你…你發誓…
Which is why l'm gonna ask you again now, under oath.
蘇西…
Suzie...
…撒母耳·倫巴多有沒有強姦你?
...did Samuel Lombardo rape you?
托樂小姐，你必須回答這個問題
Ms. Toller, you will have to answer the question.
托樂小姐. -去死吧!
-Ms. Toller. -Goddamn it!
- 這不是我的主意. - 反對，法官大人
-This was not my idea. -Objection, Your Honor.
很明顯托樂小姐正被律師誘導
Ms. Toller is clearly responding to defense counsel's badgering.
法庭很想聽聽托勒小姐說的話
Court would like to hear what Ms. Toller has to say.
托樂小姐?
Ms. Toller?
薩姆 倫巴多沒有強姦我
Sam Lombardo didn't rape me.
他也沒有強姦凱利. 他什麼也沒做
He didn't rape Kelly either. He didn't do anything.
這真荒謬，證人受到辯護律師的直接恐嚇
This is ridiculous. The witness has been threatened by defense counsel!
我已經說明了法庭將要聽取托樂小姐的陳訴
l think l made it plain this court intends to hear Ms. Toller's story.
托樂小姐
Ms. Toller.
我想傷害 倫巴多先生
l just wanted to hurt Mr. Lombardo.
他開頭是我的朋友
He was my friend at first.
後來我被抓了… 他卻不再保護我…
And then l got busted, and he didn't stick up for me...
而我不得不滾到那個鬼地方去
...and l had to go away to that hell hole.
一開始你是他的最愛，然後卻「誰管你?」
lt's like you're his favorite, and then ''Who cares?''
讓她停下來
Make her stop.
凱利 說要這麼做…
When Kelly said that we should do this...
-…我在想，「真酷.」 -凱利!
-...l thought, ''Cool.'' -Kelly!
那些大人物給找我的麻煩，像 杜奎特警官
All these big shots screwing me over, like that cop, Duquette.
-現在他們自己有麻煩了. -對不起，法官大人
-Now they're gonna get screwed. -l'm sorry, Your Honor.
我反對
l have to object.
法官大人，我能講幾句嗎?
Your Honor, please, may l be heard?
巴克斯特先生，你不負責這件案子
Mr. Baxter, you are not trying this case.
坐下
Go sit down.
凱利對 倫巴多先生也很惱火
Kelly's pissed at Mr. Lombardo too.
她愛上了他
She's in love with him.
自從她老頭死後，他是她的幻想
He's been her fantasy since her old man died.
後來她卻發現 倫巴多先生在和她媽幹，就這樣
Then she found out he was doing her mom, and that was it.
什麼? 凱利!
What? Kelly!
你這個臭婊子!
You skanky bitch!
你他媽的把手拿開!你不知道我是誰嗎?
Get your fucking hands off of me! Don't you know who l am?
-我準備週一開除你! -就這樣
-l'm gonna have you fired on Monday! -Right this way.
拿開這個破東西
Just get the hell away from me.
上帝呀，夥計! 該放鬆一下啦!
Jesus, man! Let loose!
我在想我住在哪兒
l'm just thinking about where l'm gonna stay.
我的房子沒了
l lost my house.
從這該死的惡夢中清醒過來吧
Waking up from a goddamn nightmare.
你就要熬過來了
You'll get over it.
我們給她很重的一記，案子辦得無懈可擊…
We have got a knockdown, airtight, motherfucker lawsuit...
…給桑德拉·范·賴安
...against Sandra Van Ryan.
也就是這樣
Just like that?
這些人毀掉你的生活，兄弟
These people ruined your life, bro.
我跟你說他們太過分.會走過頭的!就是沒錯!
l told you they were gonna go too far. They went overboard! They did!
他們會善後的，相信我. 他們會懇求著安排善後
They'll settle. Believe me. They'll be begging to settle.
哦好啦! 上吧! 等著吧!快點兒，寶貝
Oh, yeah! Here we go! Hey, wait up! Come on, girl.
事情驚人地變化， 薩姆 倫巴多案被駁回…
In a startling turn of events, Sam Lombardo has been dismissed...
他的一個聲稱的受害者推翻先前的證詞
...following a reversal of testimony by one of his alleged victims.
嘿，看這兒
Excuse me. Over here.
嘿.有人看報了嗎?
Excuse me. Can anybody read?
嘿! 桑德拉!
Hey! Sandra!
我真想你馬上把那訟棍的蛋釘到牆上
l want you to nail that shyster's balls to the nearest wall.
本來是可能的…
We could have, if Ms. Not-So-Bright here...
-…要是那個笨小姐不澤出這些鬼話… -我操
-...hadn't thrown things. -Fuck off.
我都不敢相信你會讓他從這個垃圾堆逃出來
l cannot believe you're just gonna let them get away with this shit!
這個最爛的雜種
All on the word of one little white-trash bitch.
我想你還沒搞明白，桑迪
l don't think you get it, Sandy.
你的寶貝女兒做了偽證
Your princess here committed perjury.
我所能做的只是讓她逃脫他媽的牢獄之災
lt'll be all l can do to keep her fucking little ass out of jail.
那我們要做什麼?
Well, what are we going to do?
- 給你咖啡. - 謝謝你
-You're gonna love this place, Tom. -Thank you.
傑珀·波克·樸萊特會殺了你
That jalape?o pork platter will kill you.
我的意思是:你不能這個星期每天都吃壽司
l mean, you can't eat sushi every day of the week.
寶登，為什麼不停下
Bowden, why don't you cut the crap...
…告訴我你的客戶究竟需要什麼
...and tell me what your client really wants.
好的，巴克斯特
Okay, Baxter.
我的客戶希望你的客戶戴上馬鞍…
My client wants your client to saddle up...
…然後我們騎在他的屁股上面直奔銀行
...so we can ride her ass straight to the bank.
你知道的，肯
You know, Ken.
我可以叫你 肯麼?
May l call you Ken?
另外的案件，另外的時間
There will be other cases, other days.
我明白…
The way l see it...
湯米
...Tommy...
…今天所有人都吃屎了嗎?
...is that everybody's gotta eat some shit sometime.
你要熱的麼?
You like yours hot?
是的
Yeah.
- 給你咖啡，薩姆. - 謝謝你
-Here's your coffee, Sam. -Thank you.
肯
Ken.
對不起我晚了
Sorry l'm late.
替我接一下電話，勒諾
Hold my calls, Lenore.
好的，寶登先生
Okay, Mr. Bowden.
謝謝你，桑德拉
Thank you, Sandra.
我會找你的
l'll be seeing you.
- 怎麼樣? - 好啊. 來吧
-Okay? -Okay. Yeah.
很高興見到你，湯姆
Nice to see you, Tom.
一起來吧 午餐
Come by. We'll have lunch.
俱樂部見
See you at the club.
俱樂部見，湯米!
See you at the club, Tommy!
嘿，湯米，今天戰績如何，朋友?
Hey, Tom. What did you shoot today, pal?
嘿，我說夥計!
Hey, my man!
這是給你的
This is for you.
-你做的很棒，肯. -是的
-You did good, Ken. -Yeah.
謝謝
Thanks.
我知道你寧願什麼事都沒發生…但它發生了…
l know there's a part of you that wishes none of this had happened, but it did.
那就拿著這錢好好享受一下
So take the money and enjoy yourself.
怎麼樣?找個好地方
All right? Find a happy place.
勒諾，送倫巴多先生出去好嗎?
Lenore, would you see Mr. Lombardo out, please?
-再見，薩姆. -再見，勒諾
-Goodbye, Sam. -Bye, Lenore.
照看好我的蜥蜴，好嗎?
Take care of my lizards?
你好，凱利
Hello, Kelly.
去死吧
Drop dead.
你知道我媽媽付給你什麼了?我的信託基金
You know how my mom's paying you off? She's breaking my trust.
她死前我動不到這些錢，但現在她賠給你
l can't touch it until she's dead, and now she's breaking it to pay you.
對不起，凱利
l'm sorry, Kelly.
為什麼你不再去幹她啊 !你們可以一起花這錢
Why don't you start fucking her again! You can spend it together!
我他媽的恨死你了，你這個雜種!
l hate you! l fucking hate you, you son of a bitch!
我恨死你了!
l fucking hate you!
你看，阿蒂?我不能再回來了，即使我想回來
You see, Art? l couldn't come back even if l wanted to.
可惡的女傭
Goddamn maid.
那麼你拿到了我媽媽的錢
So you got my mom's money.
多少?
How much?
你知道有多少
You know how much.
那該你付帳了
Your turn to pay.
成功了! 我們幹掉這個婊子啦!
lt worked! We screwed the bitch!
說的對
lt worked just like you said.
怎麼了?
What's wrong?
你他媽的把我嚇壞啦.你不該來這兒.就這個
You scared the shit out of me. What's wrong is your coming here.
你他媽的瘋了嗎?
That's what's wrong. Are you fucking crazy?
是的，我是瘋了… 去問問我媽媽
Yeah, l'm crazy. Ask my mom.
那麼，8百50萬元分成三份是多少呢?
So how much is 8.5 million divided by three?
哦，很好
Oh, great. Yeah, this is a big joke. Big joke.
都覺得很好笑嗎.你們真他媽的認為這事完了嗎?
Everyone thinks this is really funny. Do you think this is fucking over?
我告訴你們.還早著呢
Let me tell you something. lt's a long fucking way from over.
我是認真的
l'm serious.
今晚以後，我們三個不能再被人看到在一起
After tonight the three of us are not to be seen together again.
今晚以後?
After tonight?
是的，好了
Yeah, well...
…我們都在這兒了，不是嗎?
...we're here, aren't we?
也許慶祝一下也不錯…
So maybe one celebration is okay...
如果我們達成一致的話…
...if we're in agreement...
那麼從現在…
...that from here on out...
你們就要完全照我說的做
...you do exactly as l say.
法律輔導員總是很會找樂子
Guidance counselors get to find out all sorts of interesting things.
現在我要你們兩個接吻
Now l want you two to kiss.
來吧
Come on, now.
別為這事吵一天
Never let the sun go down on an argument.
我告訴過你，他們把我們當傻瓜玩
l told you they were gonna make us look stupid.
你說的沒錯.他們的確把我們當傻瓜
Hey, you're right. They did make us look stupid.
你錯在不知為什麼
What you're wrong about is why.
聽聽我的看法
All right, hear me out.
倫巴多跟桑德拉·范·賴安之間有一腿，是嗎?
Lombardo was having an affair with Sandra Van Ryan, right?
為什麼他不告訴我們?
Why not tell us about it?
要是 凱利編造的這故事這正好是個動機
That's a hell of a motive for Kelly to fabricate this story.
也許倫巴多的律師在法庭上留這一手
Maybe Lombardo's attorney was saving the affair for the trial.
我想過這些事，然後說:你是倫巴多.你已完蛋了
l thought about it and said: ''You're Lombardo. Your life is trashed.
你又不想在監獄裏熬三個月，除非--
You don't wanna sit in jail for three months unless--''
除非什麼?
Unless what?
除非你設計要桑德拉·范·賴安跟你在哪天結一個大帳
Unless you're setting Sandra Van Ryan up for the big payday.
在整個這事發生前，倫巴多已經債務纏身
Lombardo was eyeball-deep in debt before this whole thing started...
…要想繼續維持芭芭拉巴克斯特那樣昂貴的講究的生活
...trying to keep up with a pricey girl like Barbara Baxter. That's expensive.
倫巴多 可能會破產，但為什麼 凱利要偷這個錢?
Lombardo may be broke, but why would Kelly steal?
這小子拿到的這筆錢是她祖父留下的，而她在她母親去世前是不能碰它們的
Kid's got money from her grandfather she can't touch until her mother dies.
我來告訴你，這個小子本想跟有錢人結婚
l'm telling you, this guy wanted to marry money.
當這些不能實現… 他就去在這兩個女孩身上下工夫…
When that didn't happen, he went to work on these two girls...
…利用她們去算計桑德拉·范·賴安
...using them to set up Sandra Van Ryan.
我告訴你， 他當我們是白癡搭檔.
I'm telling you, they chumped us, partner.
他們從一開始就把我們當木頭.
They chumped us right from the start.
遊得不錯
Nice stroke.
你來這裏有什麼原因嗎?
ls there some reason why you're here?
-我想，是好奇. -好奇什麼?
-Curiosity, l guess. -About what?
怎麼提高你的蛙泳水準?
How to improve your breast stroke?
我好奇的是在你看來你和薩姆，蘇西三個人以後會怎樣?
No. l want to know how you see things working out for you, Sam and Suzie.
什麼意思?
Excuse me?
你們三人是想要一起到加勒比海…
You three gonna go to the Caribbean together?
從此以後過快樂生活?
Live happily ever after?
問題是三人組合很少能一直合作下去
You see, the thing about it is that threesomes rarely work out.
你丫神經病吧
You're out of your mind.
要一個人保守秘密已經很難 別提三個啦
lt's hard enough for one person to keep a secret, let alone three.
特別是當其中兩人相愛時
Especially when two of them are in love.
既然得到那些錢，你和薩姆可不想邊上有個吸毒的
You and Sam don't want that pill-head around now that you have the money.
…我說的沒錯吧?
Am l right?
薩姆幹掉蘇西前會不會跟你說一下?
Sam sell you on the idea right up front of whacking Suzie? Hey!
那會是謀殺，孩子
That's murder, kid.
上帝啊，警官，省省吧
Police. God, get a life.
你覺得很好?
You're good, you know that?
但你是不是不曾想過那個怪誕的蘇西家會成為一個阻礙?
But you don't think that little freak Suzie's gonna hold up, do you?
你好.，蘇西
Hello, Suzie.
你最好別再碰那該死的東西
You better watch it with that shit.
你又出事啦，這是第二次
You get busted again, you go back in a two-time loser.
沒錯，大不了去死
Yeah, or wind up dead.
你知道…
You know...
我想我從未告訴過你，我對你朋友的事感到有多抱歉
...l don't think l ever told you how sorry l was about your friend.
他叫什麼?
What was his name?
蘇西.你記得他名字的.告訴我
Come on, help me out here, Suzie. You know his name.
-大衛. -是的.沒錯. 大衛
-Davy. -Yeah. That's right. Davy.
我真的對那事情感到抱歉
l was sorry about the way that worked out.
- 那都是你們員警的廢話. - 你說什麼?
-That is cop bullshit. -What was that? What was that?
我再也不用聽這些 你再也別想壓著我
l don't have to listen to this. You can't shove me around.
-我現在有朋友了. -嘿!
-l have friends now. -Hey!
這是雷，蘇西. 你別想糊弄過去!
This is Ray, Suzie. You don't have shit!
你從來就混不過去， 你以後也混不掉
You never had shit and you never will have shit.
看看這個
Take a look at this.
看看.它不會咬你的
Go ahead, take it. lt's not gonna bite you.
拿著!
Take it!
你的朋友薩姆存的支票
Your friend Sam deposited the check.
他把錢轉到一個離岸帳戶，一個數字帳號
He transferred the funds to a numbered offshore account.
警局甚至不知道帳戶的名字是誰.想想其中有一個名字會是你嗎?
Cops don't know the names on it. Think one of them is yours?
他為一個小島付下定金，而且分期付款買一艘遊艇
He also put a down payment on island property and a lease on a sailboat.
你要去出海，是嗎?
You're into sailing, aren't you?
我不知道你為什麼要告訴我這些，為什麼要來這兒?
l don't know why you're telling me this. Why are you here?
我告訴你是因為我完全知道將要發生的事
l'm telling you this because l know exactly what's going on.
兩個人可以成為夥伴， 三個人就多餘了
Two's company. Three's a crowd.
現在相信我
Come on, now.
你也不認為凱利和薩姆 會和你一起分這筆錢吧?
You don't think Kelly and Sam are gonna share that money with you.
讓我單獨呆會兒
Leave me alone.
你要知道
You know...
你要知道，如果我是你，我就希望我現在腦子清醒點兒…
...l'd want a clear head right now if l were you...
這樣我就能看清楚我的新朋友
...so l could keep a real close eye on my new friends.
我不願看到你的結局那麼慘…
l'd hate to see you come to a bad end...
…就像 大衛一樣
...like Davy.
真見鬼
Oh, shit.
我是薩姆 倫巴多. 請在嗶聲後留言.
You've reached Sam Lombardo. Wait for the beep, leave a message.
我真不能相信你竟會給薩姆打電話.你到底怎麼了?
l can't believe you called Sam. What's the matter with you?
我很害怕，我不知道該相信誰
l'm scared there's no one to trust.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
喂?
Hello?
-凱利，蘇西在你這兒? - 是的
-Kelly, is Suzie there? -Yeah.
我正擔心這個.
Christ, l was afraid of that.
她給我留下個蠢話
She left this insane message.
一邊抽著那些東西
Between whatever she's been smoking out there...
…一邊是這他媽的員警.她真會搞砸掉.
...and this fucking cop, she's gonna blow it.
讓這婊子冷靜下來.
Calm the bitch down.
為什麼你不能來，求你？
Why can't you come? Please?
薩姆，我真的好想你
Sam, l miss you so much.
我也想你，凱利，但是現在不行.
l miss you too, Kelly, but l can't right now.
我們要完成計畫，好嗎?
We gotta stick to the plan, okay?
如果他媽的她不能挺住--….
If she can't get a fucking grip....
- 那怎麼樣? - 你知道怎樣.
-Then what? -You know what.
我會親自處理的
I'll handle it.
但我需要你，凱利.我要你今晚為我呆在那兒.
But l need you, Kelly. l need you to be there for me tonight.
- 好吧. - 很好.
-Okay. -Good.
這才是我的好姑娘.你很堅強，知道嗎?
That's my girl. You're the strong one, you know that?
現在叫蘇西也來聽. 我想要你們兩個都聽著.
Now, put Suzie on the line. I want you both to hear this.
蘇西.
Suzie.
薩姆?
Sam?
現在，聽著…
Now, look...
…我們要冷靜下來，我們每個人…
...we gotta stay calm, all of us.
現在，這事以後，人們都認為我很有錢了…
Now, since the settlement, people think l'm rich...
…所以我要出去大把花錢，做那些富人該做的事.
...so l'm out there spending money, doing what rich guys do.
可這個員警，他想要他媽的添亂 不能讓他得逞.
This cop, Duquette, he's gonna try and fuck with you. Don't let him.
- 你說起來容易. -蘇西，別崩潰.
-Yeah, that's easy for you to say. -Suzie, don't fall apart.
能讓這事穿幫的，只有我們自己
The only people who can fuck this up is us.
你們--你們想要甩掉我，是不是?
You are gonna fuck me over, aren't you?
去你的.
Oh, for chrissake.
就是!
You are!
你是低能啊，還是腦袋被沼氣熏昏啦?
Are you retarded, or just brain-dead from whiffing fumes out in the swamp?
我也正想這麼說你--滿腦子泥漿，就像我媽媽一樣.
That's what l am to you, isn't it? Swamp trash, just like my mom.
別碰我!
Don't!
你個瓜批!
You stupid cunt!
你很害怕，是嗎?
You are scared, aren't you?
上帝啊!
Ray! Jesus Christ!
- 你瘋了? - 你聽她在叫「薩姆」
-Are you crazy? -Hear her say ''Sam''?
它們在和 倫巴多通電話.你看這兩個女孩
That was Lombardo on the phone. And you saw the two girls.
磁帶上的談話莫名其妙
The conversation on the tape is unintelligible.
我們現在有的只是你在范·賴安 的私人產業上
What we have here is you on the Van Ryan property...
- 拍到的色情鏡頭! - 我真不能相信
-...shooting a porn flick! -l can't believe this.
一個月前，這兩個女孩還在法庭上大打出手
A month ago, they threw things at each other in court.
她們在演戲! 他們都在演戲!
They were acting! They were all acting!
我們卻相信它，深陷其中
We bought it, hook, line and sinker.
現在他們要帶著桑德拉·范·賴安的8百萬美金逃跑
They're getting away with $8 million from Sandra Van Ryan.
她想保住的那些錢，她沒有計劃去毀掉這個男人的生活
She might have saved it if she didn't try to ruin him.
如果你認為那小子強姦你的女兒，你還會去追求他?
You wouldn't go after a guy you thought raped your daughter?
她也像我們一樣相信了那些鬼話!
She bought the same goddamn story we did!
你們兩個聽著，你們不是在辦一個案子，因為現在沒有他媽的案子
Both of you, you're not on a case, because there is no fucking case!
我很清楚桑德拉·范·賴安這個人，如果你繼續這樣在她家周圍晃來晃去…
l've had it with Sandra Van Ryan, and you keep mucking around...
…那她一定會去控告我們非法侵入
...and she's gonna sue us for invasion of privacy.
所以不要理這些人的事! 嘿! 雷!
So get out of these people's lives! Hey! Ray!
- 我說清楚啦? - 你覺得這只是涉及到錢?
-Hey! Am l getting through? -You think this is just about money?
大概我們看起來很蠢?問問這個人吧
About us looking stupid? Question him.
你會發現有個變態狂在背後控制，那些女孩將會走向死路
You'll find a manipulative psychopath, and those girls will wind up dead.
給這個蠢貨一點事去做吧
Give him something to do.
- 也許該讓他去調查甘迺迪的謀殺案. - 我明白
-Look into the Kennedy assassination. -l understand.
下次這個混蛋…
Next time this fucking piece of shit...
再在這兒拖住我，我會去控告你
...drags me down here, l'm gonna sue you.
這次你混蛋夠運，我最後一次放過你
You're goddamn lucky l didn't sue last time.
- 我明白. - 我現在可以走啦?
-l agree. -Am l free to go?
- 是的. - 謝謝
-Yes. -Thank you.
- 操蛋 - 你說什麼?
-Cocksucker. -Yeah, what was that?
- 你聽見啦，傻屄 - 你敢當我面再說一遍?
-You heard me, motherfucker. -Yeah, you wanna say that to my face?
你看什麼呢?
What are you looking at?
- 我猜我可能會被調離這裏. - 可以這麼說
-l guess l kind of lost it out there. -You could say that.
你有過這樣的事?你明知道有些事會發生…
Were you ever in a situation where you saw something coming...
…而你可以阻止的，卻不去做你該做的
...and you didn't do what you could to stop it?
我們都有此經歷
We all have.
我是說你看到一件壞事，然後它發生了…
l mean something bad that you saw coming, and then it happened...
可你卻什麼都不能做，而且--
...and you-- You didn't do anything, and....
我遇到過一次
l did that once.
我不想再來一次
l don't wanna do it again.
我還以為我們要去看電影
l thought we were going to a movie.
我想我們只是需要打發時間
l think we just need to get wasted.
快來
Yeah.
Come on.
我希望有一天我能住在海邊
l wanna live at the beach someday.
噢，糟糕
Oh, shit.
我忘了鑰匙
l left the keys.
我去拿
l'll get them.
凱利?
Kelly?
蘇西
Suzie.
是我
lt's me.
我很擔心你，所以我決定…
l was worried about you, and l decided...
在分手之前，我們三個應該再聚最後一次
...the three of us should get together one last time before we split up.
-你對我很生氣嗎? -不.不
-Are you mad at me? -No, no.
我也許應該多告訴你一些關於…
l probably should've told you a bit more about...
…我準備要演的角色
...the part l intended to play.
但我們今晚要來一次
But we'll go through it again tonight.
慶祝一下，而不是自殺約會
This is a celebration, Suzie, not a suicide pact.
我們要涼快一下只要放鬆一點…
We're gonna chill out and just relax...
…來一點兒香檳…
...have a little champagne...
…看看星星…
...watch the stars....
凱利?
Kelly?
在你媽媽的車後備箱裏找到毯子啦?
You got a blanket in the back of your mom's Rover?
行行好，再去幫我們拿來?
Why don't you be an angel and run over and get it for us?
好姑娘
Good girl.
給你說說我為我們精心挑選的這條船
Let me tell you about the boat l picked out for us.
你還好?
You okay?
要是我媽知道我開走她的車，她會殺了我的
My mom would kill me if she knew l took the Rover.
四輪?
Been four-wheeling?
-離開我的屋子! -我沒在你的屋子裏面
-Get off my property! -l'm not on your property.
-如果你不離開這裏-- -你要報警麼?我就是員警!
-lf you don't get out of here-- -You'll call a cop? l am a cop!
我操!
Goddamn it!
你是說她昨晚沒回家
So you say she didn't come home last night.
她是一直說要去洛杉璣，但她的衣服全都在這裏
She's been talking about going to L.A., but her clothes are all still here.
沃爾特! 你有病啊，它們用得好好的
Walter! You get sick, it'll serve you right.
找些倒在路上的老流浪漢的的牙齒
Found some teeth in an old trailer down the road.
他說他們很合適
He says they'll fit.
審判結束後，蘇西就沒回學校
Suzie hasn't been back to school since the trial.
哦，現在他們肯定在說她不能畢業
Oh, and now they're saying that she can't graduate.
這都是 凱利 范·賴安帶她陷進去的，你們都知道
lt is that Kelly Van Ryan that got her into this whole mess, and you know it.
我們會查的，魯比
Well, we'll look into it for you, Ruby.
如果我們發現什麼，你會第一個知道
We find something, you'll be the first to know.
走啦
Come on.
現在開始啦，格洛裏亞. 這就是開始
lt's starting, Gloria. This is how it begins.
我們根本不知道什麼. 她也許在別的任何地方
Ray, we don't know anything yet. She could be anywhere.
我會在警局放下你， 打電話查一下蘇西的車
l'll drop you off. Put a call out on Suzie's car.
你要去什麼地方嗎?
You got someplace you wanna be?
-你有約會? -你只要幫我查出這輛車
-You got a date? -Just check the car out for me.
在那艘舊船那兒
lt's over here, by that old boat.
那你和蘇西來過這兒?
So you and Suzie used to come out here together?
是的，有時候
Yeah, sometimes.
有許多小子都來這兒
A lot of the kids hang out here.
你真得覺得蘇西出事啦?
You really think something bad happened to Suzie?
倫巴多來過這裏?
Lombardo ever come out here?
我說了什麼好笑的事?
l say something funny?
不是，我只是說，這樣想 倫巴多先生也太 --
No, but l mean, just the idea that Mr. Lombardo would--
好吧，我聽到一些，他和孩子們的關係不錯
Well, the way l heard it, he was pretty tight with the kids.
你和他是朋友對吧?
You and him were pals, right?
是的，是他讓我來航行組的
Yeah, but he got me onto the sailing team.
告訴我說我可以靠自己的努力完成學業，就像他那樣
Told me l could work my way through college, like he did.
薩姆 倫巴多 是靠體育獎學金上的邁阿密大學…
Sam Lombardo went to the University of Miami on an athletic scholarship.
這些船可跟這該死的事無關
Boats didn't have a damn thing to do with it.
我會在這裏呆一會兒，孩子
Listen, l'm gonna be here a while, kid.
你去高速公路上趕公共汽車吧?
Why don't you go up to the highway and catch the bus?
嘿，吉米
Hey, Jimmy.
人並不總像他外表的那樣. 記住這句話
People aren't always what they appear to be. Don't forget that.
- 這就是作案現場. - 屍體在哪兒?
-This is where they did it. -Where's the body?
在沼澤裏，很可能 這小子是個沼鼠
The swamp, most likely. Guy's a swamp rat.
他知道在這裏屍體不會被發現， 但他犯了一個錯誤
He knows it won't be found, but he made a mistake.
她祖母說過她感到很危險，所以想跑掉…
She'd been threatening to run away and l found the car at the bus terminal.
你不認為是山姆把它停在那裏的?我在公共汽車總站發現她的汽車
You don't think Sam put it there?
稍等一下. 格洛裏亞，給那輛車噴點灰取印模
Hold on a second. Gloria, have the car dusted for prints.
如果蘇西真的被謀殺， 一定是那個范·賴安 小混蛋幹的
And if Suzie even was murdered, it was that damn Van Ryan kid.
一個小叛逆從一開始就註定啦
Little sociopath's the one who started this.
- 我們多長時間可以拿到結果? - 我們可以立刻拿到血型的報告
-How long till we get something? -We can get blood type now.
核對牙齒記錄時間要長些. DNA的測試結果要幾個星期
Dental records will take longer. DNA could take weeks.
可憐的笨蘇西. 從來不曾有過機會
Poor, dumb Suzie. Kid never had a chance.
- 我們還不知道什麼. - 讓我告訴你，凱利 就是下一個
-We don't know that. -l'm telling you, Kelly's next.
讓我來告訴你，離開這裏… 馬上
l'm telling you, you get off this right now.
別他媽的讓我聽到你再去打擾倫巴多
Don't even fucking let me hear about you bothering Lombardo.
大衛
David!
你拿到身份報告，直接通知我!
You get an lD, you call me!
幫我一個忙好不好?
Will you do me a favor?
雷，你聽到他說的
Ray, you heard him.
他只是說讓我不要碰倫巴多， 關於你他倒是什麼都沒說
He told me to stay away. He didn't say anything about you.
想想如果我正確而亨特錯怎樣
What if l'm right and Hunter's wrong?
求你，這次你得幫我
Please, you gotta help me out on this, partner.
如果這牙齒不是蘇西的， 你得放棄這想法?
And if the teeth aren't Suzie's, you'll give this up?
如果這次我錯，我聽你的
lf l'm wrong about those teeth, you got my word.
-喂? -我給你你打過電話.
-Hello? -I've been calling you.
-我想見你. -你在哪兒?
-l wanna see you. -Where are you?
-這該死的客人房 -好的.呆在那兒.
-The stupid guest house. -Good. Stay there.
薩姆，我真的很緊張
Sam, l'm really nervous.
凱利，放鬆點
Kelly, relax.
吃一片你媽媽的鎮靜藥什麼的
Take one of your mom's Valiums or something.
一個星期後，當你乘上飛機， 這些就結束了.我們就有錢啦
ln a week, you get on the plane, this is over. We're rich.
但是如果他們發現了呢?
But what if they find out?
上帝，他們會把你推上電椅
My God, they'd put you in the electric chair.
聽著，凱利…
Look, Kelly...
…今晚呆在那裏，想想畢業舞會
...stay in the guest house, skip the graduation parties.
我非常愛你
l love you so much.
我也愛你，凱利.
And I love you too, Kelly.
做個好姑娘 呆在那兒.
Be a good girl and stay where you are.
在別人的窗戶外面偷窺…
Peeping in people's windows?
…是不是違法的?
lsn't that against the law?
蘇西·托樂 失蹤了
Suzie Toller's missing.
- 什麼時候? - 她昨晚沒有回家
-Since when? -She didn't come home last night.
我們在公共汽車終點站發現她的汽車
We found her car at the bus terminal.
雷 認為她已被害
Ray thinks she was murdered.
我不知道該說什麼
Well, l don't know what to tell you.
你可以告訴我你昨晚在哪兒
You could tell me where you were last night.
我想我能告訴你， 但我真得沒必要這麼做，是不是?
l suppose l could, but l don't really have to, now, do l?
來這兒
Come here.
我給你看樣東西
l wanna show you something.
看起來像是準備離開
Looks like goodbye.
凱利的檔案
Kelly's file.
讀讀看. 你會發現這是個憤怒的，性困惑的女孩…
Read it. You're gonna find an angry, sexually confused girl...
…至少有兩個人使得她對生活產生恐懼
...who threatened the lives of at least two people.
哪兩個人?
What two people?
其中一個是她母親
One of them was her mother.
另一個是…
The other one was...
…她的一個女同學…
...a female classmate...
…和她可能有些複雜的性關係
...she may have been sexually involved with.
蘇西?
Suzie?
現在你拿著這個檔案
Now you got the file.
看看它
Read it.
我想它會讓你對此事有新的看法
l think it'll give you a new perspective on things.
為什麼你在審訊前不告訴我們這些?
Why didn't you tell us about this before the trial?
因為那時我還有些個人守則
Because then l had principles.
對我來說很重要的
That meant a lot to me.
但現在…
Now...
…我不再在乎
...l don't care.
我也許應該走
l should probably go now.
除非你打算找些什麼事留住我
Unless you're planning on holding me for something.
-杜奎特.發生什麼事? -我很累.我回家啦.
-Duquette. What's happening? -I'm tired. I'm going home.
-倫巴多在哪? -走了…
-Where's Lombardo? -He's gone.
日，格洛裏亞，岩石上的血型跟蘇西吻合
Goddamn it, Gloria, the blood type on the rocks matches Suzie's.
我來告訴你一些事情，雷:
Let me tell you something, Ray:
關於這件事，有許多是你不清楚的
There's more to this story than you know.
如果蘇西死掉了…
If Suzie is dead...
…亨特 可能要盯上 凱利.
...Hunter may be on the right track about Kelly.
雷?
Ray?
混蛋，雷
Shit, Ray.
-是誰? -杜奎特偵探
-Who is it? -lt's Detective Duquette.
開門
Open the gate, now.
-你好，凱利. -你來這兒幹什麼?
-Hello, Kelly. -What are you doing here?
哪裏--? 凱利! 凱利!
Where's--? Kelly! Kelly!
我只是剛一轉眼，也就一眨眼的時間
l just looked away for a second, just a split second.
就是那樣-- 就來啦--
And just like that, bingo...
…她用膝蓋頂我的腹股溝
...she put a knee in my groin.
我開始沒倒下，慢慢地往下-----
l didn't go down, but it slowed me down...
…就這樣
...just enough.
我碰不到她
l couldn't get to her.
她拿把槍對著我
She turned on me with the gun.
開一槍
Fired one shot.
我躲一下打中肩膀
l took the hit in the shoulder.
我沒別的選擇
l had no choice.
只能開槍還擊
l had to return fire.
兩槍，我想是，打中胸部
Two rounds, l think, in the chest.
我去那兒是想保護她的
l went there to protect her.
我--我去那兒是想保護她的
l went-- l went there to protect her.
杜奎特偵探
Detective Duquette.
我曾在軍事情報局幹過一段時間， 在那兒我們有個說法:
l spent time in military intelligence, and we had a saying there:
一次是偶然. 兩次是巧合
''Once is happenstance. Twice is coincidence.
三次是敵意
Three times is enemy action.''
你現在已經兩次，杜奎特…
This is twice for you, Duquette...
所以我不想看到第三次
...and l intend to see to it that there is no third time.
我們調查認為你打的很準， 這個有點無關緊要
Our investigation finds that this was a good shooting, but that's irrelevant.
但你忽視上級的指示
You ignored the advice of your superiors.
從而，造成兩個年輕女孩的死亡
Consequently, two young women are dead.
從現在開始，你被停職. 同時終止你的養老金和福利金
You are, as of now, terminated, with forfeiture of pension and benefits.
勾賽爾局長…
Chief Goodsall...
…杜奎特偵探發現 蘇珊·瑪麗·托樂的牙齒和血跡…
...Detective Duquette found Susan Marie Toller's teeth and blood...
就在被叫做碎石海灘的地方
...near the area known as Stoner Beach.
越野車裏也發現托樂的血跡
Miss Toller's blood was also found in the Van Ryan Range Rover.
這讓警方認為…
This has led this office to conclude...
蘇珊·瑪麗·托樂 是被 凱利·拉尼爾·范·賴安謀殺的
...that Susan Marie Toller was murdered by Kelly Lanier Van Ryan.
她- 她沒有
She-- She didn't.
杜奎特先生
Mr. Duquette.
調查結束 你可以走啦
This investigation is concluded. You're dismissed.
謝謝你，保羅
Thank you, Paul.
你好啊，搭檔
Howdy, partner.
上帝啊，你這傢伙.我還以為你明天來
Jesus, man. l wasn't expecting you until tomorrow.
看，你的好女友打的
Hey, nice girlfriend you got there.
凱利本來只是要當個頂罪的
Kelly was only supposed to be framed.
這婊子開槍打我
The bitch shot me.
該死，你是個員警. 難道他們沒有教你讓人解除武器?
Shit, you're a cop. Don't they teach you to disarm people?
你知道 打腿或者類似地方?
You know, shoot them in the leg or something?
你忽然有點多愁善感啊
Did you become squeamish about this stuff before or after...
…是在你用葡萄酒瓶當敲死小蘇西之前還是之後?
...you bludgeoned little Suzie to death with a wine bottle?
我們沒有安排凱利 死掉，雷. 這不是計畫裏的
Kelly wasn't supposed to die, Ray. lt wasn't part of the plan.
夥計，事情也不會更好啦. 他們相信是凱利謀殺的蘇西
lt couldn't have worked out better. They're convinced Kelly killed Suzie.
我不能告訴他們實情
l couldn't talk them out of it.
我只想告訴你，我不喜歡意外
l'm telling you, l don't like surprises.
你應該這樣看這件事:每朵烏雲都有金邊
Look at it this way: Every cloud has a silver lining.
現在再不會有破綻
Now there's no loose ends.
明天來，你就再也別看到我
Come tomorrow, you'll never see me again.
好吧，聽聽看，要明天
Oh, listen, about tomorrow...
…我已經對銀行講過但他們說， 需要兩個工作日…
...l spoke to the bank and they said it's gonna take two working days...
…來完成轉帳，所以--
...to make the transfer, so....
-胡說 -哦，是的
-Bullshit. -Oh, yeah.
你可以自己打電話
Call them yourself.
不管怎樣，還急啥呢? 等個一兩天
Anyway, what's your hurry? Kick back for a day or two.
我們駕船出海吧. 我剛把船裝配好
We'll take out the boat. l just had it outfitted.
我也許還需要個水手
l could use a deck hand.
這是兩個大筆的銀行帳戶
Here's to large bank accounts.
你應該輕鬆一下，夥伴. 你是個富人了
You gotta lighten up, partner. You're a rich man.
兩個大筆的帳戶，而且毫無破綻
To large accounts and no loose ends.
毫無破綻
And no loose ends.
嘿，雷，看見那個絞盤啦?
Hey, Ray, you see that winch?
拿這個工具去擰一下. 船要全速向風
Take a couple turns on it. She's luffing.
- 你是說那個東西? - 沒錯. 雷
-You mean that thing? -Yeah, Ray.
我們管它叫絞盤，用它來拉緊船帆
We call it a winch. lt's what we use to tighten the sails.
- 那為什麼不開始幹呢? - 我們把這看成一個假期呀
-So why don't you start cranking? -This is supposed to be a vacation.
為什麼你不去弄艘好的機動船呢?
Why don't you get a nice powerboat?
來啊，雷. 我會讓你成為一個真正的水手的
Come on, Ray. l'll make a sailor out of you yet.
或者讓我淹死
Or get me drowned.
它鏽住啦
lt's stuck.
你說什麼?鏽住? 稍微用點兒力吧
What do you mean, it's stuck? Put a little elbow grease in it.
鏽住啦，我告訴過你
lt's stuck, l'm telling you.
得把帆腳索綁在什麼東西上
The jenny sheet must be caught on something.
那你去右舷看看你是否能把它解下來?
Why don't you go starboard and see if you can unhook it?
- 你說的我一句也聽不懂. - 好吧，雷
-l don't understand a word you said. -Okay, Ray.
你看見那根繩子? 看看它下頭…
You see this line right here? Follow it down...
看看它是否被什麼纏住
...and see if you can see what it's snagged on.
你會害死我
You're killing me.
-這個東西? -就是它.就在那兒
-You mean this thing? -That's it. That one right there.
看到東西了麼?
You see anything?
再向下看一點兒
Look a little lower.
就這樣
That's it.
我忘告訴你，雷:
Guess l forgot to tell you, Ray:
一隻手管船， 一隻手管自己
One hand for the boat, the other one for yourself.
航海的第一準則
First rule of sailing.
雷!
Ray!
-怎樣啦? -很不錯啊，操他奶奶的
-What happened? -Nice try, motherfucker!
是你!
You!
你已經死啦
You're dead!
不，我沒死
No, l'm not.
薩姆
Sam.
-薩姆，該死的! -對不起，搭檔
-Sam, for chrissake! -Sorry, partner.
你真的不該殺凱利
You really shouldn't have killed Kelly.
你也不該在那片沼澤地裏殺死那個孩子
You shouldn't have killed that kid out in the glades either.
-他的名字? -大衛
-What was his name? -Davy.
那是我兒子沃爾特，沃爾特
That's my son, Walter.
他做這工作很久，所以你們不用害怕. 請吧，請進
He's been doing this a long time, so don't be afraid. Please, come on in.
謝謝光臨沼澤地
Thank you so much for coming down to the glades.
你是來這裏看沃爾特表演的，還是公事?
Did you come here to watch Walter, or is this an official visit?
不，事實上，今天我休息
No. Actually, it's my day off.
我覺得你看起來不大一樣
l thought you looked different.
我來這兒是因為我希望你能跟我說說
l came because l was hoping you would talk to me.
關於蘇西?
About Suzie?
事實上，我希望你能說說雷 杜奎特
Actually, l was wondering if you would talk to me about Ray Duquette.
他過去常來這裏
He used to come around here.
他跟其中的一個女孩有些關係--
He had a thing going with one of the girls--
沼澤地周圍這些女孩
Girls. Over at the glades.
從我聽到的好像是跟她鬼混
Got sort of hung up on her, from what l hear.
- 她仍在那兒工作? - 從那晚以後就沒有
-She still work there? -Not after that night.
我只知道，第二天早上…
All l know is, the next morning...
她離開，但一個男孩死啦
...she was gone and a boy was dead.
是個塞米諾爾族人，名字叫大衛. 他迷上雷的婊子
Seminole kid named Davy. He had a crush on Ray's whore.
他看到雷抽她，他想管一檔
Caught Ray slapping her around, and he tried to stop it.
所以雷把他殺啦
So Ray killed him.
蘇西 看到
Suzie saw it.
所以他逮捕她，然後又保釋她
So he busted her and sent her up.
你知道那僅僅為證明他有這個能力
You know, just to prove that he could.
雷 杜奎特就是這樣的
That's all there is to say about Ray Duquette.
為雷
To Ray.
我們贏啦薩姆，現在結束啦
We won. Sam, it's over.
像個妄想狂 看看我們周圍，薩姆
Wow. Talk about paranoid. Take a look around us, Sam.
即使我要除掉你，你也要先教會我操縱這船啊
You're gonna have to teach me how to drive this before l can get rid of you.
好吧，托樂
Okay, Toller.
我想整好船帆. 抓住那個絞盤
l wanna trim the sail. Grab a hold of that winch.
-去它的絞盤.我想要駕駛. -不是那樣的
-Fuck the winch. l wanna drive. -lt doesn't work that way.
你不是駕駛它，你要使它揚帆航行
You don't drive it, you sail it.
現在去抓住絞盤
Now, get on that winch.
我想要巡航一會兒
l just wanna cruise for a while.
這很有意思. 這是我注意到你的第一件事，薩姆
That's funny. That's one of the first things l noticed about you, Sam.
你喜歡巡航
You like to cruise.
-蘇西. -拿大學期間舉個例子
-Suzie. -Take college, for instance.
我打賭你在那兒選修的課程都是多項選擇的結果
l bet the classes you took were ones where the finals were multiple choice.
而且你從不買書. 你只是尋找一個女孩…
And you never bought the book. You'd find a girl to loan you hers.
她把書借給你，然後你跟她上床，對不對?
And then, of course, you'd have to fuck her after that, right?
是這樣度過的?
ls that how it went?
是的
Yeah.
好吧，我現在有個測試題來問你
Well, l've got a good pop quiz for you.
當然也是多重選擇
Multiple choice, of course.
在駕船逃向赫利俄斯之前…
Before sailing on the Helios...
…美狄亞殺死克瑞翁王和公主… 用的是什麼?
...Medea killed King Creon and the princess with what?
一塊石頭…
A rock?
一把長矛，還是…
A spear gun?
一點兒毒藥?
Or a little poison?
毒藥!
Poison!
猜的好
Good guess.
范·賴安老了
Van Ryan got old.
他和他的老友會來這裏
He and his cronies would come here.
狩獵和嫖娼. 真他媽的狗屎
Hunt and whore. They acted like a bunch of assholes.
一次旅行，他和這個女孩出現了…
One trip, he showed up with this girl...
…他從某地溝上她
...he'd picked up somewhere.
並讓他懷孕
Gotten her pregnant.
在沼澤地宰了她
Dumped her in the swamp.
可憐的姑娘死了一年…
Poor girl was dead in a year.
和她一起
That came with her.
小孩呢?
And the child?
在她喝死自己之前已經有了
Well, she had it. Before she drank herself to death.
確實不是個可愛的小孩
Wasn't exactly a love child.
所以你不是她奶奶
So you're not her grandmother.
我培養了他像我一樣
l raised her like l was.
但是.不.沃爾特是我唯一的孩子，一個好男孩
But, no. Walt was my only child. He was a good boy.
直到他參軍
Until the Army took him.
所以蘇西 還有桑德拉·范·賴安算是半個姐妹
So Suzie and Sandra Van Ryan were half sisters.
另一個女孩，凱利? 蘇西的外甥女
And the other girl, Kelly? Suzie's niece.
這算是好消息還是壞消息. 我不知道.我們會用信件開始
Well, it may be good news or not. I don't know. We'll start with the letter.
-H. -是的.兩個H.
-H. -Yes, there are two H's.
卡車不錯啊
Nice truck.
要賣你的船?
Selling your boat?
這個是蘇西的船
This was Suzie's boat.
我猜她現在不需要它啦
Guess she won't be needing it now.
真奇怪… 我從未想到蘇西會是個水手
Funny. l wouldn't have guessed Suzie was a sailor.
老女人給她做過一次測試 她們說她的智商很高
Old lady had her tested once. They said her lQ was way up there.
大概是200或類似這些玩意
Around 200 or some such shit.
她只要用心可以作好任何事
That girl could do just about anything she put her mind to.
嘿
Hi.
你幹什麼?
What are you doing out here?
我準備離開
l'm running away.
你認為這樣明智麼?
You think that's wise?
猜猜還有什麼
Guess what else?
我有玩具
l have toys.
我建議一次嘗鮮不要去傷害
l suppose one taste won't hurt.
你知道麼…
You know...
我被抓住的時候，我給你打過一百次電話
...that weekend l got busted, l called you about a hundred times.
我真的以為你這個廢物是我的朋友
l really believed that stuff about you being my friend.
我太天真
Was l naive.
我不知道怎樣照的更好:
l can't decide what came out better.
在凱利鼻子上面粘些小草 還是找個狗項圈套在你脖子上
That little straw up Kelly's nose or that dildo shoved up her ass.
你覺得怎樣 倫巴多先生?
What do you think, Mr. Lombardo?
看起來好像是你做過同樣的事情
Seems to like the same places you do.
-有趣吧，你過去從未見過. -是的，真得有趣
-Funny you never met. -Yeah, real funny.
你知道嗎，這點上你想的不對 我會在現場被逮捕
You know, you're wrong about this, and l could get busted on the spot.
信我.這個小子很壞.他喜歡做那些壞事，他愛那些事. 特別是殺死我的那個安排
Trust me. The guy's dirty. He'll love it. Especially the part about killing me.
現在走吧. 去找個新朋友吧
Now, get out of here. Go make yourself a new friend.
你在喝什麼呢?
What are you drinking?
我們準備停了.我來了高潮
We gotta stop. l'm gonna come.
從未在沼澤擔心你
That never seemed to worry you at the glades.
-不是你的線…. -說你愛我
-That's not your line.... -Say you love me.
我愛你. 給我
l love you. Now, give me the line.
小女孩不會給我高潮的…
No little girl can ever make me come.
你的鉗子夾的太緊 你會把這證物弄碎的
You got the pressure too tight. You're gonna crush the evidence.
噢，該死的
Oh, for chrissake.
- 你好，凱利 - 你來這兒幹什麼?
-Hello, Kelly. -What are you doing here?
可以問你個問題嗎，托樂小姐?
May l ask you a question, Ms. Toller?
你喜歡來法庭做客嗎?
Did you enjoy being a guest of the state?
我希望我沒使你瘋狂
l hope l never make you mad.
現金是讓你周遊世界的
Cash is just walking-around money.
支票是帳戶上剩餘的錢…
The check is the balance of the numbered account...
…除去留給魯比  和沃爾特的一百萬…
...minus the million we set aside for Ruby and Walter...
…還有一點我的常規收費
...less my usual fee.
案子結束
Case closed.
蘇西
Suzie.
好好過
Be good.